National Council for the Traditional Arts (NCTA) collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Performer and Genre Lists
  - Genres
Jerry, Buddy and Zoomer
Jesse McReyonlds & the Virginia Boys
Jesse Smith and Colm Gannon with Michael Smith and
Jesse Smith and Colm Gannon with Smith-Houlihan Ac
Jigs and Reels in Different Cultures
Jim Payne and Fergus O'Byrne
Jimenez, Flaco
Jiménez, Jr., Santiago
Jiménez, Jr., Santiago & Su Conjunto
Jimenez, Juan
Jiménez, Jr., Santiago
Santiago Jiménez Y Su Conjunto
Jimmy Edmonds
Jimmy Noonan, Conor McCarthy, Tony Cuffe, & Chris McGrath
Jinny Marsh's Hot Kugel Klezmer Band
João Oliveira Santos
Joaquin Brothers with Nacho Armenta, The
Diaz, Joaquin
Joaquin Diaz Band, The
Joe "GRKMANIA" Grkman Polka Band
Joe & Antoinette McKenna with Mary Bergin
Joe & Antoinette McKenna with Mary Bergin, Jesse S
Joe and Antoinette McKenna
Joe and Antoinette McKenna, James Keane and Brendan Mulvihill
Joe and Odell Thompson, John Dee and Janice Holeman
Joe Cormier Band, The
Joe Cormier Band, The with Paulette Bissonnette
Joe Cormier Trio, The
Joe Derrane & John McGann
Joe Dossett & The Mighty Coachmen 1994 NFF
Joe Miller and Newman Young
Joe Montana & the Roadrunners
Joe Thompson
John Ashby and the Free State Ramblers
John Ashby and the Free State Ramblers with Appalachian dancers
John Berry
John Delafose and the Eunice Playboys
John Edmonds and the Gospel Truth
John Fritzler & The Polka Band
John Fritzler Band
John Jackson & Bill Neely
John Whelan Band
Johnnie Johnson
Johnny Florez Quartet, The
Hot Club of Cowtown with Johnny Gimble
Johnny White & the Country Masters
Johns, Altona
Johnson Mountain Boys
Johnson, Larry
Johnson, Luther "Guitar Junior"
Johnson, Luther Guitar Junior & The Magic Rockers
Johnson, Rev. C. J.
Johnson, Robin
Johnson, Vesta & Hall, Stephen
Johnstown Area Button Box Club
Jones, Buster B.
Jones, Lyndon
Jones, Suzie
Jones, Will
José Alberto "El Canario" & Su Orquesta
José Alberto "El Canario" Justiniano
José Gutiérrez Y Los Hermanos Ochoa
José Gutiérrez, Oliverio Lara, Cesareo Ramón
Josee Vachon and Florence Martin
Joseph Cormier, J.P. Cormier, Hilda Chaisson-Cormi
Joseph Stands with Many
Joseph, Henry
Josh Goforth & New Direction
Juan Gutiérrez & Los Pleneros de la 21
Julia Parker
Junior Appalachian Musicians
Junior Daugherty and Atchafalaya
Junior Daugherty Band, The
Junior Daugherty, Tammi Daugherty and Lou Reid
Junior Daugherty, Tammi Daugherty and Ted Smith
Junior Daugherty, Tammy Daugherty and Wayne Henderson
Junior Kimbrough & The Soul Blues Boys 1994 NFF
Junior Sisk and Rambler's Choice
Junkyard Band, The
Ka'apana, Ledward
Kalama, Mealii
Kalongji, Hussen
Kamae, Eddie & The Sons of Hawaii
Kane, Raymond
Kapelye
Karan Casey Band
Karl & The Country Dutchmen
Kasparian, Alice Odian
Kathryn Tickell Band, The
Kavanagh, Tom
Keane, James and Brendan Mulvihill
Keane, Seán
Keane, Seán 1999 LFF
Keating, Paul
Keawe, "Auntie Genoa"
Keenan, Jim
Keeping It In the Family
Keezer, Clara Neptune
Kegg, Maude
Keith Frank & The Soileau Zydeco Band
Kékélé
Kelly, James
Kelly, Jimmy
Kelly, Liam
Kementzides, Ilias
Kementzides, Ilias and Panayiotis Vassiliades
Kendra & Troy MacGillivray with Wendy MacIsaac
Kenmille, Agnes "Oshanee"
Kennedy, Norman
Kennedy, Roger
Kenny & Amanda Smith Band
Kenny Bill Stinson and the Ark-La-Mystics
Kenny Sidle and Darlene Underwood
Kentuckians
Kentucky Colonels
Kermit Ruffins and the Barbecue Swingers
Kevin Locke with Dale Weasel and Jennifer Weasel
Kevin Naquin & The Ossun Playboys
Kevin Peters & Gayle Ross
Keys, Will
Khang, Chia Yang and Yang Fang Nhu
Khánh Vân
Khmer Classical Ballet
Khmer Classical Dance Ensemble
Khmer Classical Dance Troupe
Khmer Traditional Arts Ensemble
Khmer Traditional Music Ensemble
Khovalyg, Kaigal-ool
Kieran O'Hare & Friends
Kieran O'Hare, Jesse Smith, Nigel Stevens
Kilby, Steve
Killen, Lou
King Memphis
King, B.B.
King, Don
Kings of Harmony
Kirchen, Bill
Kirk and Lisa Sutphin, Eddie Bond and Dale Morris
Kirk, Eddie, & Lisa
Kirkpatrick, Rev. Frederick Douglass
Kirkpatrick, Robert
Klancik, Gaylord
Klezmatics, The
Klezmer Plus
Knight, Pat
Knott, Sarah Gertrude
Knowles, Liz
Ko Nimo And His Adadam Agofomma
Kohn, Josh
Konte, Alhaji Bai
Kornrich, Bill
Kostas Taslis Band, The
Kotchegna Dance Company
Kouyate, Djimo
Krader, Barbara
Krajewski, Randy
Krauss, Alison
Krilich Brothers Band
Krishnan, Durga
Kroger, R.B
Kuralt, Charles
Kuular, Oleg Ochurovich
Kvalheim, Ethel
Kweskin, Jim
Kyvelos, Peter
Kzirian, Andrew
L.C. Donatto Band
La Bottine Souriante
La Familia Valera Miranda
La Famille Beaudoin
LaBeef, Sleepy
LaBlanc, Pastelle
Lally, Michael
Lamas of the Drepung Loesling Monastery
Lambert, Yves
Lamey, Doug
Lamond, Mary Jane
Landry, Stephane
Lang, Julian
Laotian Classical Music and Dance
Laotian-American Organization of Lowell
LaPrelle, Elizabeth
Larry Bannock and the Golden Star Hunters
Larry Gillis Band
Larry Sigmon & Barbara Poole
Larry Sparks and the Lonesome Ramblers
Larue, Clara
Laryea Addy Family
Last Train Home
Laurie Lewis & Grant Street
Laurie Lewis and Dudley Connell
LaVette, Bettye
Lawrence, Jack
Lawson, Doyle
Lawtell Playboys
Lay, Linda
Le Band Feufollet
Le Thi Thuy-Van
Le Vent du Nord
LeBlanc, Rachael
Ledward Ka'apana with Clyde "Kindy" Sproat
Lee Boys
Lee, Albert
Lee, John
Lee, Thomas
Left-Handed and Upside Down Instrument Workshop, T
Legault, Benoit and Landry, Stephane
Legendary Orioles, The
Leggat, Janet
Leggat, Sue
Len Graham & Pádragín Ní Uallacháin
Lenny Gomulka & the Chicago Push
L'Ensemble Quebecois
L'Ensemble Quebecois with Nicole Bombardier & Cara Blaise
Leonard Grenier
Les Danseurs Quebequois
Les Franco-Americains
Les Fréres Brunet
Les Gens De Mon Pays
Les Pieds Rigoiants
Les Ross, Sr. Ja Ystävat
Levendes Orchestra, The
Lewis, Steve
Liars Contest
Liberty Cornet Band
Licht, Mike
Likely, Albert
Li'l Rascals Brass Band
Lindsey, Malda
Linnehan, Jay
Lira Tamburitza Orchestra
Lithuanian Dancers of Chicago
Lithuanian Folksong Quartet
Little "Milton" Campbell
Little Milton with special guest Fontella Bass
Little Nell Walker Show
Little Wonder Boy and the Spiritual Voices
Little, Jeff
Little, Linda Grubb
Littlefield, Esther
Livesay Quartet, The
Liz Carroll and Dáithí Sproule
Liz Carroll and Her Lost Band
Liz Carroll and John Doyle
Liz Carroll, Billy McComiskey, and Daithi Sproule
Ljubica Tamburitzan Orchestra
Lloyd, Tim
Lo Jai
Lobodzinski, Adele
Local Folks from Mountain View Arkansas
Locke, Jimmy
Locke, Kevin
Lockwood, Yvonne
Logan, Adele
Lohman, Jon
Lomax, Alan
London, Lou
Lonesome Drive
Lonesome River Band
Long Haul Singers
Longoria, Valerio
Lonnie Brooks Blues Band
Looping Brothers
Loose Gap Loafers
Loose Strings
Lorraine Jordan & Carolina Road
Los Alegres De Taos
Los Bandits
Los Camperos de Nati Cano
Los Campesinos de Michoacan
Los Cantores Guaranies
Los Carácuaros
Los Coyotes Del Chamizal
Los Fantasmas del Valle
Los Fuertes de Colombia
Los Macondos de Colombia
Los Paisanos
Los Pleneros de la 21
Los Pleneros De Yucayeque
Los Pleneros Del Batey
Los Pleneros del Coco
Los Pleneros del Coqui
Los Pregoneros Del Puerto
Los Pregoneros del Puerto - 1992 CA Gen
Los Pregones Jarochos
Los Reyes De Albuquerque
Lost and Found
Lost Bayou Ramblers
Louisiana Aces
Louisiana Aces with Tony and Dewey Balfa, The
Louisiana Bouillabaisse
Louisiana Red
Love, Kenny
Lovell, Jesse
Lowell Angkor Dance Troupe and Traditional Music Ensemble
Lowell Cambodian Dance Troupe & Classical Music Ensemble
Lowery, Robert
Loyd, Jim
Lu Peng
Luandrew, Albert (Sunnyland Slim)
Luderin Darbone & Edwin Duhon
Lujan, Joaquin "Jack"
Lúnasa
Lundy, Ted
Lundy, TJ
Luring ducks, tourists, and antique collectors: changes in decoy carving
Luster, Mike
Lustre Kings
Lynn Morris Band
LynnMarie
MacArthur, Margaret
MacDonald, Bonnie Jean
MacDonald, Howie
Macedonians, The
MacGillivray, Troy
Machen, Alton
MacIsaac, Dave
MacIssac, Wendy
MacMaster, Natalie
MacNeil, Paul
Maddox, Rose and the Southern Mountain Boys
Maddox, Rose with Bob and Dan Paisley
Madison Hummingbirds
Maggie Ingram & the Ingramettes
Magic Slim and the Teardrops
Mahal, Taj
Mahotella Queens
Mahovlich, Walter
Mahusky, Terri Lynn
Maine Fiddlers Convention With Monique Leger
Maine French Fiddle Masters
Mainer Family, The
Mainer, Wade
Mainers, The
Makredes Ensemble
Mal Barsamian Ensemble with Richard Berberian
Malianek. Tony
Malone, Conor
Moloney, Mick
Malpass Family Band
Mamadou Diabate Ensemble
Mami Cann & Janine Faley
Mancuso, Acosta & McLoughlin
Mando Mania: Mandolin Apprenticeships
Mangan, Patrick
Manh Câm and Trân Thao
Manigault, Mary Jane
Manning, Frankie
Marcel Robidas & Milton Appleby
March, Rick
Marchand, Paul
Marcus Santos & BatukAxé
Mardi Gras Indians
Maria Baeza & Maria Leyro
Mariachi El Capiro De Jalisco
Mariachi Guadalajara
Mariachi Jalisco
Mariachi Los Amigos
Mariachi Los Camperos de Nati Cano
Mariachi San Matías
Mariachi Tapatío
Mariachi Vargas
Mariamova, Freida
Marimba Chiapas
Marimba Chiapas led by Lorenzo Cruz
Marimba Continental
Marimba Linda Xelajú
Marion, Florence
Marion, Paul
Mark Halata & Texavia
Markic and Zagger Orchestra
Marnce, Reverend Albert
Marshall Brothers
Marshall Heights Young Adult Choir
Marshall, Janice
Martell, George
Martha & Emily Spencer
Martin Breakdown
Martin Hayes and Dennis Cahill
Martin Hayes and Dennis Cahill with Áine Meenaghan
Martin Mulhaire, Michael Preston & Jimmy Kelly
Martin, Bogan & Armstrong
Martin, Carl
Martin, Florence
Martin, Lynn
Martin, Reed
Martinez, Esther
Martinez, Guillermo
Martinez, Maria Ester and Mariachi America
Martinez, Melecio
Martínez, Roberto
Martinez, Roberto & Lorenzo
Marva Wright & the BMWs
Mary Bergin and Antoinette McKenna
Mary Jane Lamond and Friends
Mary Jane Queen (family)
Maryland Pacesetters Steel Orchestra
Masabi Candyman
Mason, Eileen B.
Massingale, Dwayne
Masters Of Cape Breton Music And Dance
Masters of Caribbean Music
Masters of Mexican Music Tour Musicians 2004
Masters of the Banjo
Masters of the Folk Violin 1988 Cast
Masters, Mack
Masters, Mack and Baxter Wareham
Matapat
Matas, Tito
Mathieu, Lucien
Matos, Diomedes
Matteo Casserino and Gino DiMichele
McAdams, Eva
McAuley, Mick
McAuley, Oisin
McCain, Jerry
McCain, Jerry with Big Chief Ellis and the Barrelhouse Rockers
McCain, Jerry with Henry Townsend and Big Chief Ellis with Vernell Townsend
McCarthy, Benny
McCaslin, Mary
McClain, Mary E. Smith
McClellan Family
McClellan, Mike
McClinchey, Brendan
McComiskey, Billy
McComiskey, Sean
McCord, May
McCoury, Del
McCoy, George and Ethel
McDermott, Alice
McDonald, Marie
McFarvis Family Fiddlers
McGee, Dennis
McGee, Dennis, Sady Courville and Marc Savoy
McGlynn, Sean
McGreevy, Johnny
McGuire, Jim
McHale, Linda
McHenry, Tom
McIntire, Will
McIntosh County Shouters
McIntosh, Sylvester
McIntyre, Chuna
McKeen, Smokey
McKenna, Antoinette
McKenna, Joe
Joe and Antoinette McKenna
McKenna, Joe and Antoinette & Ciaran
McKennas, McGlynn, Carroll, Henry and Flatley
McKennas, The
McKenney, Al
McKenzie, Joey
McKnight, Baile
McLaughlin, David
McLeod, Zan
McMahan, Pete and Charlie Walden
McMillon, Bobby
McPeak Brothers
McPeake, Jimmy
McQuillen, Bob
McQuin, Audrey
McRae, Wallace
Mead, Chuck
Meade, Don
Meadows, Phil
Meagher, Tim
Mealing, John Henry & Wright, Jr., Cornelius
Meeley, John
Meenaghan, Aine
Melgaard, Leif
Melodic Improvisation Workshop
Melody of China
Men in Black
Men of Steel: Slide Guitar Styles
Menard, D.L.
Menard, D.L. & The Louisiana Aces
Menard, D.L. with Vin Bruce and the Acadians
D.L. Menard, Dewey Balfa and the Louisiana Aces
Mencher, Sean
Mendoza, Lydia
Mendoza, Lydia with Trio San Antonio
Menhaden Chanteymen
Mentrotone Baptist Singers, The
Mentrotone Volunteer Choir
Merakia Orchestra, The
Merakia, La
Mertz, Van
Messick, Walter
Methe, Claude
Metheny, Josh
Mexican Dancers, The
Michael & David Doucet
Michael Flatley and The Freeborn Irish (FBI)
Michael Flatley, Kevin Henry, Jimmy McPeake, Sean McGlynn, Liz Carroll
Michael, Jeff
Michaels, Jack
Choiniere, Michele
Michigan Heritage Award Winners 2000
Michot Brothers
Michot, Andre
Michot, Louis
Mick Moloney, Zan McLeod, Jerry O'Sullivan
Mighty Sparrow
Mighty Walker Brothers, The
Mike and Mary Rafferty
Mike Francis And His Sunshine Dixieland Jazz Band
Mike Piorek Orchestra, The
Miller, Eli
Miller, Gerald "Subiyay"
Miller, Norma
Miller, Rodney
Milner, Chuck
Milt and Laura Appleby and Joe Pomerleau
Ming, Hoyt and the Pep Steppers
Mingo Saldivar y Los Cuatro Espadas
Mingo Saldivar y sus Quatros Tremendas Espadas
Mingo Saldivar y sus Tremendos Cuatro Espadas
Mingo Saldivar y sus Tremendos Cuatros Espandas-2001
Miousse, Pascal
Miranda, Edgardo
Mirko Roknich Orchestra
Missouri Fiddlers
Mitchell, Bernice
Mitchell, Waddie
Mitiebi Choir
Moges Seyoum & Yared Choir
Moilanen, Art
Molina, Celso
Moloney, Mick
Moloney, O' Connell, & Keane
Molton, Flora
Montana, Allison "Totie"
Montanaro, Karen
Montgomery, Little Brother
Moore, Alex Sr.
Moore, Dorothy
Moore, Juanita
Moore, Ray
Moore, Ronnie
Moose Family
Morehouse, Spelman and UTC Step Show
Morella, Connie - US Congresswoman
Moreno, Carmencristina
Morgan Heritage
Morgan, Vanessa Paukeigope
Morin, Mac
Morris Brothers with Jenkins and Sherrill
Morris, Willie
Morrison, Harold and the Smoking Bluegrass
Morse, Captain Kendall
Moss, Buddy
Mougin, Genevieve Nahra
Mountain Heart
Mountain Music with Dick Albin and Friends
Mountain Songs & Ballads
Mountain Strings
Mountain Voices: From Appalachia to Altai
Moving Cloud
Moving Star Hall Singers
Mua, Bua Xou
Mukti
Mulkerrin, Mick
Muller, Bobby
Muller, Ceil
Mulsky, Bruce
Mulvihill, Brendan
Mulvihill, Martin
Mulvihill, McComiskey, & McLeod
Munson, Fatima
Murphey, Bob
Murphy, Grainne
Murphy, Jimmy
Murphy, John Robert
Murphy, Mabel E.
Murphy, Maureen O'Rourke
Murray, Carmen
Muse, Lewis "Rabbit" Anderson
Music from the Crooked Road
Music, Dance and Song from the Island of Karpathos
Muzhiteno Nerekhtski Horn Ensemble
Muzhiteno Choir
Muzhiteno Choir and Nerekhtski Horn Ensemble
Mythili Prakash & the Dance of India Ensemble
N.B.S
Na'ope, George
Nadeem Dlaikan
Nadia Dieudonne & Feet of Rhythm
Nadim Dlaikan and Friends
Nahwooksy, Fred
Nakasone, Seisho "Harry"
Namu Lwanga & Impala
Naquin, Kevin
Nashville Bluegrass Band
Nathan and the Zydeco Chachas
Neely, Bill
Nego Gato Afro-Brazilian Ensemble, The
Negron-Rivera, Julio
Nerekhtski Horn Ensemble
Nevaquaya, Doc Tate
New River Plateau
New Ballard's Branch Bogtrotters
New Camp Creek Players
New Emage
New England Pentecostal Crusade Choir
New Harp Singers Of East Tennessee
New Lost City Ramblers
New Orleans Klezmer All Stars
New Pasqua Yaqui Troupe
New River Bluegrass
New River Grass
New River Plataea Railroad Band
New Trends In Banjo
New United Senior Choir
New York City Brass Entourage
New York Goofs
Newsome, Frank
Newsome, Lay & Whitesell & Whitetop Mountain Band
Next Generation
Next Generation Harpists
Next Generation WIF 1999
The Next Generation
Nez, D.J.
Nez, Grace Henderson
Ngek, Chum
Nguyen Dinh Nghia Family
Nic Amhlaoibh, Muireann
Nicholas Benson
Nicholson, Barbara
Nicolo Whimsey
Nieto, Gustavo
Nikitina, Svetlana
Nile Ethiopian Ensemble
Nilemma Devi Dance Troupe
No Speed Limit
Nomos
Nona & Apprenticita: F. Jagoda & S. Gaeta
Non-Chicago Irish
Noon, Rosemary
Noonan, Jimmy
Bruso, Nora Jean
Norberto Tavares and Tropical Power
Norkunas, Martha
Norman & Nancy Blake w/James Bryan and Tom Jackson
Norman Kennedy and Cliff Haslam
Norred, Mike
North Carolina And Virginia Old Time Banjo Workshop (NFF 1978)
Northern Neck Chantey Singers
Nukariik
O'Donnell, Eugene
Obey, Dave
Obey, Dave & The Capitol Offenses
Obo Addy & Okropong
O'Brien, George
O'Connell, Robbie
Odadaa
Odadaa! International
O'Hare, Kieran
Ohio Fiddlers Convention
Ohio Jazz Masters, The
Ohrlin, Glenn
Oinkari Basque Dancers
Gaupasa and the Oinkari Basque Dancers
Oklahoma Native American Color Guard
Old and in the Way
Old Blind Dogs
Old Grey Goose Variety Show, The
Old Harp Singers Of East Tennessee
Old New England
Old Time String Band
Old Time Tradition
Olde Michigan Ruffwater String Band, The
Older, Larry
Oldtime Boys
Olin, Julia
Oliver Mtukudzi & Black Spirits
Olympian Brotherhood
Olympic Melodies
Omer Forster, Houston Daniels and The Highland Rim Boys
O'Neill-Abraham, Paula
Opacich, Milan
Orchestra Tamo Daleko
Orchestra Vasiliadis Petros
Original Grecian Keys, The
Oriskany Strings
Ortega, Dick
Ortega, Luis
Ossian
Otonowa
Otter Creek Singers
Ouellette, Lionel and Dufresne, Leo
Our Lady Of The Angels Band
Owens, Vernon
Owusu, Kwabena
Ozark, Appalachian, Irish and Cumberland Ballads
P.J. Hernon & Swallow's Tail Céilí Band
Paddy Glackin and Robbie Hannan
Padillo, Martin C.
Pahinui, Cyril
Paisley, Bob and Dan
Paisley, Dan
Palabuniyan Kulintang Ensemble
Pan Masters Steel Orchestra
Panegyri
Panopoulos Brothers Orchestra
Panorama Steel Band
Panygiri
Papantla Flyers
Paquin, Rita
Paquito D'Rivera and the United Nation Orchestra
Parker, Diana
Parker, Mac
Parker, Molly Neptune
Paschall Brothers, The
Pasha, Annie
Pashia, Charlie
Pasha, Jim
Pashia, Charlie
Pasley, Randy
Passing It On
Passing The Bow
Pat Courtney Gold
Pat Managan & Zan McCeod
Patrick Street
Patton, Gary
Paul Dahlin & the Edwin Johnson Family Fiddlers
Paul Dahlin and the Äkta Spelman "the genuine fiddlers"
Paul, Carline
Paulin Brothers Brass Band, The
Pearl River Social Dancers
Pearson, Barry Lee
Pearson, Barry Lee and Craig James (or Jones)
Pearson, Segrid
Pedro Ayala, José Salinas, Juan Viesca
Peebles, Ann
Peeples, Charlene
Peg Leg Sam
Peirce, Maggi
Peltier, Maurice
Pendleton, Buddy
Penitentes of New Mexico
Pennington, Alonzo
Pennington, Eddie
Pennington, Eddie and Family
Penny Whistle Workshop
Pennywhistlers, The
People of Olympus, The - Greek Islanders in Baltimore and their Arts
Peou, Khatna
Perdue, Chuck
Perdue, Chuck and Nan
Perez, Irvan
Perfume River Ensemble
Perkin's Band
Perkins, Joe Willie "Pinetop"
Persuasions, The
Peter Rowan and Jerry Douglas
Peters, Kevin
Peterson, Zack
Petric, Faith
Philadelphia Folksong Society
Philip "Olumide" Gilbert
Phillips, Cora Lee
Phipps Family
Phong Nguyen
Phong Nguyen Trio
Phong T. Nguyen
Piano Masters
Piano Red (William "Willie" Lee Perryman)
Piano Styles
Piano Styles from Cape Breton to California
Pickett, Josh
Pidkivka, Andrei
Piedmont Blues
Piedmont Buckdancers, The
Piedmont House Party
Pierson, Leroy
Pilarinos, Konstantinos
Pilgrim Travelers
Pilot Mountain Bobcats
Pina, Johnny
Pinckney, Mary
Pine River Boys and Maybelle
Pineconers
Pinettes Brass Band
Pinettes, The
Pinewoods Folk Music Club of New York City
Pinkham, Ron
Pinnacle Boys, The
Pipe Traditions
Piping Workshop
Plainsmen, The
Playing The 88s
Pleasants, Dick
Po D Terra - Joao Cerilo
Poast, Ron
Poetry in Motion
Polisar, Barry Louis
Polish Heritage Choir
Polish Highlanders
Politcal Leader-Local
Politte, Joe
Polka Cuzzins
Polka Family Band
Polka Workshop
Ponleur Cheath
Pontiakon-Somation
Pool, Lena Thomas
Preacher Jack
Precious Bryant and Neal Pattman
Prem Nymith
Prem Raja Mahat
Presnell, Nettie
Preston Frank and the Zydeco Family Band
Pribich, Djoko
Price, Fred
Price, James
Price, Kenny
Pride of New York Ceílí Band
Prillaman, Ted and the Virginia Ramblers
Principles, The
Prine, John
Prochan, Frank
Proffitt, Frank Jr.
Proschan, Frank
Pueblo of Laguna Dancers
Puny Pickers
Purkey, Elaine
Puryear, Jeb
Puryear, Mark
Pushpanjali Dance Group
Putnam, Dr. John F.
Putnam, John
Qi Shu Fang
Quartet Singing Styles Workshop
Quebe Sisters
Quebecois & Maritime Dance Session
Queen Ida and the Bon Temps Zydeco Band
Quimby, Frankie & Doug 1994 NFF
Quinn, Bobby
Rachel LeBlanc, Lucie Quellette & Jimmy Kelly
Rachell, Yank and J.T. Adams
Radost Orchestra
Rafferty, Mike
Raga & Rhythm Ensemble
Raghavan, Jothi
Raíces Musicales Tour 1988 Cast
Ralph Stanley & the Clinch Mountain Boys
Raman, R.V
Rambur, Rich
Ramsey, Buck
Ramudi Sapera and Party
Rancho Folklorico de Hartford
Randy & Deborah Jean Sheets
Rankin Family, The
Rankin, Mairi
Rascoe, Moses
Rastetter, Tim
Rath, Steve
Ravanese, Dave
Ray Dorschner's Rainbow Valley Dutchmen
Raymond Street Klezmer Band, The
Raz de Marée
Rebirth Brass Band
Rebirth Jazz Band
Recitations From East And West
Red Clay Ramblers, The
Red Rector, Don Stover, Don Gulley
Red Rector, Don Stover, Don Gulley and Junior Daugherty
Red Rector, Don Stover, Don Gulley, Junior Daugherty and Gene Daniels
Red Stick Ramblers
Redd Volkaert Band with Cindy Cashdollar
Reed Island Rounders
Reed, Mitchell
Reed, Ola Belle
Reels Jigs And Breakdowns (NFF 1977)
Reeltime Travelers
Reese Brothers
Reese, Jerry
Reese, Nat
Reillys, Musselman, & Acosta
Reily, Steve
Reisman, Isidore
Relatives of the Guitar
Religious Instrumental Music Workshop (NFF 1978)
Remington, Herb
Reuben Sarkisian and Friends
Reverend Nathaniel and Sister Fleta Mitchell and Doc and Lucy Barnes
Rex and Eleanor Parker
Reyes, Koren
Reyes, Frank
Reynolds, George
Reynolds, John
Rhodes, Dr. Willard
Rhythm In Shoes
Ricardo Lemvo & Makina Loca
Richard Felts Orchestra
Richard Hagopian Trio
Richard Hagopian with Hachig Kazarian
Richard Wood & Brenda Stubbert
Richard, Jay
Richards, Sue
Richardson, John
Richens-Timm Irish Dancers
Richmond Indigenouse Gourd Ensemble
Riddle, Almeda
Riley, Marie
Riley, Steve
Ringer, Jim
Rinzler, Ralph
Ritachka, Roman
Ritchie, Fiona
Ritchie, Jean
Rivers, Mike
Rivers, Reverend Boyd
Roan Mountain Hilltoppers
Robert Turner & the Silver Hearts Gospel Singers
Roberto Borrell Y Su Kubatá
Roberts, Dalton
Roberts, Kenny
Roberts, Leonard
Roberts, Page S.
Robertson, Brooks E.
Robertson, Lonnie & Thelma
Robichaud, Gerry
Robinson, Debbie
Robinson, LaVaughn
Rock Bottom
Rockin' Dopsie And The Zydeco Twisters
Rockin' Dopsie and the Twisters
Rodney Miller & Airdance
Rodriguez, Eliseo & Paula
Rodriguez, Juan
Rodriguez, Rodney
Rogers, Grant
Roheim, Anund and Anna
Rohman, John
Roland L. Freeman
Romero, Emilio and Senaida
Romero, Herminia Albarrán
Ron Thomason and John Baker
Ronnie Reno & Reno Tradition
Roots of Blues Workshop
Roots of Brasil
Roots of Rock'n'Roll NFF 1993
Roots of the Banjo
Rorick, Dorothy
Rorrer, Kinney
Rosado, Emilio
Roseman, Jason
Rosie Ledet & the Zydeco Playboys
Rosin The Bow
Rosman, Michael
Ross County Farmers
Ross, Gayle
Ross, Pete
Rossi, Neil
Round Knob Singers
Round Peak Ramblers
Round, Jay
Rouse, Don
Roussos, John
Roussos, John and Friends
Roy Sisters
Roy, Broto
Roy, Don
Roy, Khan, & Shashidhar
Royal Lao Traditional Music & Dance
Roz de Ma
Ruak, Felipe & Joseph
Rubber City Retreads, The
Rucker, Sparky
Rug Hooking Interview
Rugby Roustabouts
Rumisongos
Rutherford County Square Dancers
Saari, Wilho
Sabor Latino
Sacks, Howard
Sacks, Judy
Sacred Harp Singer
Sacred Harp Singers of FS of GW
Sadeghi, Manoochehr
Saldivar, Domingo "Mingo"
Saldivar, Mingo
Sam Brothers Five, The
Sam, Calvin
Samba Ngo And The Ngoma Players
Samite of Uganda
Sammy Shelor & Kirk Sutphin
Sample, Tim
Samten, Losang
Sand Mountain Harp Singers
Sanderford, Mark
Sanderson, Chris
Sandra Piechocki
Sankofa Strings
Santha, Dolores
Santiago Jiménez, Jr. Y Su
Saolin Hong Gar Martial Art Academy
Sapera, Rumudi
Sapoznik, Henry
Sapoznik, Zindel
Sarbinska, Tatiana
Sarkisian, Reuben
Saturday Night, Sunday Morning Cast
Sava
Savoy Family Band
Savoy, Marc
Savoy, Marc & Ann with Florence Martin
Savoy, Marc & Ann with Ken Smith
Sayles, Charlie
Scandinavian Dancers of St. Paul
Scanlon, Dierdre
Schmitt, Dorado
Schneyer, Helen
Schwartz, Teddi
Schwarz, Tracy
Scoggins, Earl
Scotch Irish Tunes Workshop
Scott, Jeff
Scottish Country Dance Society of Washington DC
Scottish Dancers of Chicago
Scotty & Patsy East
Scruggs, Earl
Seamus Connolly & Donald Clancy
Seamus Connolly & Paul MacDonald
Seamus Connolly and Friends
Seamus Connolly and Friends w/Joe Derrane
Seamus Egan & Solas
Seamus Egan & Winifred Horan
Seamus Egan and John Doyle
Seamus Egan, Eileen Ivers, Dave MacIsaac
Seán Keane and Frank Kilkelly
Seán Keane Band
Sean Mencher Combo
Seán Nos Singing Workshop
Sears, Ken
Seceri Orchestra
Secretary Norman Mineta
Seeger, Mike
Seeger, Pete
Seemann, Charlie
Segelstein, Cookie
Segura, Chris
Seiichi Tanaka
Sekatau, Ella
Seldom Scene, The
Sellars, Celestar
Selma Jam Session
Sensacion Vallenato con Gustavo Nieto
Sensational Nightingales, The
Sevag, Armen
Severe, Duff
Sexton, Morgan